http://www.uniteunion.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
UNITE HERE has created this privacy notice to explain how we use the information you may provide while visiting our Website and/or visiting UNITE HERE’s accounts on third-party websites (such as Facebook and Twitter), and to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. UNITE HERE may modify this policy from time to time, so we encourage you to check this page when you return.
The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Website and for information that we receive from third-party websites. The type and amount of information UNITE HERE receives from you depends on how you use the site(s).
Website Use and Information Collection
When you visit the UNITE HERE Website, we automatically obtain information from you about the name of your Internet service provider, the browser and type of computer you are using, the Website that referred you to us, the pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. We use this information in aggregate to generate statistics and measure site activity so we can improve the usefulness of the site to our visitors. For example, we use this information to track which pages are most popular among visitors as a whole. We do not track the pages you or any individual visitor may look at during a visit to our site, and we do not collect any other information without your knowledge and permission. We do not collect or store personally identifiable information, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, or phone number unless you provide that information.
Collecting Personally Identifiable Information
UNITE HERE provides web forms so you may provide your contact information to engage in UNITE HERE activities such as online activism (e.g., contacting Congress) or to correspond with UNITE HERE. Any information we collect—such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, type of request you are making, or any additional information you provide—is collected and stored by UNITE HERE. The information is used to fulfill your request and track aggregate information about how our visitors use these features. If you do provide your e-mail address, we may collect individual information on whether you open e-mails that we send to you.
Our Website and services are not directed to people under age 13. On all areas of our Website, we seek to collect personally-identifiable information only from adults; we do not knowingly collect or store any personally-identifiable information from anyone under age 13.  If we become aware that someone under age 13 has submitted any information to us without prior, verifiable, parental consent, we will delete the user’s information. Please contact us if you have any concerns that we have any personally-identifiable information from anyone under age 13.
Collection of Personally Identifiable Information from Third-Party Websites
Please note that third-party websites generally have their own privacy policies that apply to any information that you share on such websites. UNITE HERE is not responsible for how information is collected and shared by third-party sites. This privacy policy only applies to information provided to UNITE HERE through your use of third-party sites.
When you provide information on UNITE HERE pages or accounts on third-party websites, that information may be shared with UNITE HERE. For example, when you digitally sign Twitter petitions sponsored by UNITE HERE, and elect to share your name and email address with UNITE HERE, Twitter will send us your name, twitter handle, and e-mail address on the account you have with Twitter.
Any information we collect, including your name, twitter handle, e-mail address, type of request you are making, and any additional information you provide, is collected and stored by UNITE HERE, and may be shared as described below. The information is used to fulfill your requests and track individual and aggregate information about usage of these features. UNITE HERE makes every effort to ensure the secure collection and transmission of your sensitive information through password-protected storage of your information.
Our accounts, pages, and services offered on third-party websites are not directed at persons under age 13. We seek to collect personally-identifiable information only from adults; we do not knowingly collect or store any personally-identifiable information from anyone under age 13.  If we become aware that someone under age 13 has submitted any information to us without prior, verifiable, parental consent, we will delete the user’s information.
Sharing Personally Identifiable Information
UNITE HERE may share personal information with other labor organizations if we believe you would be interested in receiving their communications. An example of this partner sharing would be with your own union Local, for example.
We also provide personal information to third parties on a completely confidential basis to enable a third party to perform certain tasks, such as maintain a membership database or send email alerts and/or newsletters, on our behalf. These third party providers are committed to protecting the privacy of our members and subscribers and will not use your information for any purpose other than what is necessary to deliver the services we contract with them to provide.
UNITE HERE’s website will not post your personal contact information, including e-mail address, street address, and phone numbers, without your consent. Without such consent, Website staff will withhold posting personal contact information for that individual.
Finally, while UNITE HERE will object to all requests for access to information about users of our sites that we believe to be improper, we may disclose information when we have a good faith belief that doing so is required by law, such as pursuant to a subpoena or judicial or administrative order. If we are required by law to disclose your information, we will try to provide you with notice (unless prohibited), to give you an opportunity to object to the request. If you have provided us with an email address, we will attempt to contact you by email if you have given us an email address, or by regular mail if you have given us a mailing address.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s hard drive containing information about them. The UNITE HERE Website uses a cookie for measuring aggregate statistics, including our number of monthly visitors, repeat visitors, most popular pages, and other information. UNITE HERE will also use cookies so that you will not need to resubmit certain information you provide for online activism. UNITE HERE does not use cookies to track which specific pages an individual site visitor views.
Opting Out of E-mail Lists
People who subscribe to e-mail lists via the UNITE HERE Website will receive periodic updates from UNITE HERE. You may opt out of receiving future information via e-mail by using the unsubscribe procedure specified in the e-mail.
Opting Out of Text Message Updates
People who subscribe to text message updates will receive periodic updates from UNITE HERE. You may opt out of receiving future information via text message by texting “Stop” to 877877 or replying “Stop” to a text message from UNITE HERE. We will honor such requests within 30 days.
Outside Links
This site contains hypertext links to other sites. UNITE HERE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.
Security
UNITE HERE has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, including password-protected storage of all e-mail information. If you send us an e-mail or submit your name, email, or zip code through our website, you should know that the form and e-mail are not necessarily secure against interception. So, if your communication includes sensitive information like your bank account, credit or debit card, or social security number, please contact us by mail or by telephone rather than through the website contact form or by e-mail.
Correcting or Updating Personal Information
If your personal information changes (such as your ZIP code), or if you wish to have your information removed from our database, please contact us and we will correct, update, or remove the personal data provided to us.
Contact Us
If you experience technical problems with the operation of this Website, please e-mail akammerer@unitehere.org.
www.unitehere.org
Web Editor
UNITE HERE International Union
1775 K Street NW Suite 560
Washington, D.C. 20006
Phone: 202-393-4373
You also may contact us by mail or telephone. If you do so, we may use the information you provide in the ways we have described in this privacy policy.
Find Your UNITE HERE AffiliateUNITE HERE represents workers throughout the United States and Canada.
Find a Local by State/ Province
Local 1 Chicago, Illinois
Karen Kent, President
218 S Wabash, Suite 700
Chicago, Illinois 60604
US
http://www.unitehere1.org
Tel. 312-663-4373
Eric Gill, Financial Secretary-Treasurer
1516 S. King St.
Honolulu, Hawaii 96826
US
http://www.unitehere5.org/
Tel. 808-941-2141
Fax 808-941-2166
Email: egill@5.unitehere.org
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/uniteherehawaii
Twitter: @uniteherehawaii
Local 8, Oregon and Washington
Portland Office,
1125 SE Madison Ave., Ste 209
Portland, Oregon 97214
US
Tel. 503-230-2304
Fax 503-230-0542
Email: erik@unitehere.org
Local 11 Los Angeles, Orange County, and Arizona
Ada Briceño, Susan Minato, Kurt Petersen, Co-Presidents
Email: cmello@unitehere.org
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Unite-Here-Local-17/179716465404606
Local 19 San Jose, Fresno-Yosemite, San Luis Obispo, Santa Barbara
Enrique Fernandez, Business Manager
2302 Zanker Road, Second Floor
San Jose, California 95131
US
http://www.unitehere19.org
Tel. 408-321-9019
Fax 408-321-9029
Email: elfernandez@unitehere19.org
LaToya Colvin, Chapter President
502 1st Ave.
Columbus, Georgia 31901
US
Local 23 Tunica, Mississippi
Mary Reynolds, Chapter President
PO Box 667
1195 Main Street
Tunica, Mississippi 38676
US
Fax 604-291-2676
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Unite-Here-Local-40/129648666837
Twitter: @UNITEHERE40
Local 41 Saskatchewan
Garry Whalen, President
320 Longman Crescent
Regina, Saskatchewan S4N 6J7
Canada
Tel. 306-781-8157
Fax 306-543-3856
Email: chrisrak@unitehere.org
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/UNITE-HERE-Local-49/132232743518155
Local 54 Atlantic City
C. Robert McDevitt, President
1014 Atlantic Ave
Atlantic City, New Jersey 08401
US
http://www.uniteherelocal54.com
Tel. 609-344-5400
Fax 609-572-5120
Fax 212-399-3005
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Unite-Here-Local-100/157829137588444
Twitter: @unitehere100
Local 150 Syracuse
Ann Marie Taliercio, President
615 W. Genesee St.
Syracuse, New York 13204
US
Tel. 315-426-7836
Fax 315-422-4096
Email: herelocal150@igc.org
Local 165 Las Vegas
Terry Greenwald, Secretary-Treasurer
4825 West Nevso Drive
Tel. 775-689-8670
Hospitality & Service Trades Union, Local 261 Ottawa, Ontario
Ian Robb, Trustee
200 Cooper Street Suite 2
Ottawa, Ontario K2P 0G1
Canada
http://www.hstu261.org
Tel. 613-238-8136
Fax 613-238-5499
Email: hstu261@gmail.com
Email: info@uniteherephilly.org
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Unite-Here-Philadelphia/205739642795251
Twitter: @uniteherePhilly
Local 355 Greater Miami and Ft. Lauderdale
Wendi Walsh, Secretary-Treasurer
871 NW 167th Street
Miami Gardens, Florida 33169
US
Tel. 305-614-0377
Fax 305-620-0434
Fax 215-440-0376
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Unite-Here-Philadelphia/205739642795251
Twitter: @uniteherePhilly
Local 688 Bay City, Michigan
Mary Thompson, Secretary-Treasurer and Business Agent
1300 West Thomas Street, Suite A
Bay City, Michigan 48706
US
Tel. 989-686-6496
Fax 989-686-5855
Fax 907-277-8595
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/Unite-HERE-Local-878-Alaska/368870489822511
Twitter: @UNITEHERE_AK
Local 2850 Oakland, California
Wei-Ling Huber, President
1025 3rd St.
Oakland, California 94607
US
http://www.unitehere2850.org
Tel. 510-893-3181
Fax 510-893-5362
Email: whuber@unitehere.org
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/UniteHere2850
Twitter: @UNITEHERE2850
Fax 617-426-1653
Local 281 Cambridge, Brookline, Newton, Boston, Massachusetts
New England Joint Board
33 Harrison Avenue 8th Floor
Boston, Massachusetts 02111
Tel. 617-426-1515
Fax 617-426-1653
Local 311 Lawrence, MA and Hudson, NH
New England Joint Board
33 Harrison Avenue 8th Floor
Donate to Support Hospitality Workers
COVID-19 is hitting the 300,000 UNITE HERE members especially hard. As business pauses in hotels and convention centers, sports and event venues, casinos, and restaurants, working families face layoffs and uncertainty.
You can help  by donating to the UNITE HERE Education and Support Fund.
Donate
×
